o4af.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Opportunity for Afghanistan

## Privacy Policy

The privacy of your personal information is very important and will take it seriously. Hence, we strive to provide a safe, secure user experience.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  _[Opportunity4af@gmail.com](mailto:Opportunity4af@gmail.com) _

This document governs the privacy notice of our website [www.o4af.com](http://www.o4af.com/)

Our privacy notice tells you what personal data (PD) and non-personal data (NPD) we may collect from you, how we collect it, how we protect it, how we may share it, how you can access and change it, and how you can limit our sharing of it. Our privacy notice also explains certain legal rights that you have with respect to your personal data. Any capitalized terms not defined herein will have the same meaning as where they are defined elsewhere on our website.

## YOUR RIGHTS

When using our website and submitting personal data (PD) to us, you may have certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other laws. Depending on the legal basis for processing your PD, you may have some or all of the following rights:

**The right to be informed**

** ** You have the right to be informed about the personal data we collect from you, and how we process it.

**The right of access.** _ _

You have the right to get confirmation that your personal data is being processed and have the ability to access your personal data.

**The right to rectification.**

_ _ You have the right to have your personal data corrected if it is inaccurate or incomplete.

**The right to erasure (right to be forgotten).  **

You have the right to request the removal or deletion of your personal data if there is no compelling reason for us to continue processing it.

**The right to restrict processing.  **

You have a right to ‘block’ or restrict the processing of your personal data. When your personal data is restricted, we are permitted to store your data, but not to process it further.

**The right to data portability.  **

You have the right to request and get your personal data that you provided to us and use it for your own purposes. We will provide your data to you within 30 days of your request. To request your personal data, please contact us using the information at the bottom of this Privacy policy.

**The right to object.  **

You have the right to object to us processing your personal data for the following reasons:

  * Processing was based on legitimate interests or the performance of a task in the public interest/exercise of official authority (including profiling);
  * Direct marketing (including profiling); and
  * Processing for purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics.
  * Rights in relation to automated decision-making and profiling.

**Filing a Complaint with Authorities.**

** ** You have the right to file a complaint with supervisory authorities if your information has not been processed in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation. If the supervisory authorities fail to address your complaint properly, you may have the right to a judicial remedy.

## DEFINITIONS

**Non-personal data**  (NPD)

NPD is information that is in no way personally identifiable.

**Personal data**  (PD)

PD means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person. PD is in many ways the same as Personally Identifiable Information (PII). However, PD is broader in scope and covers more data.

A  **Visitor**

A visitor is someone who merely browses our website.

## What are covered in OUR PRIVACY POLICY?

  * Information We Collect
  * Our Use of Cookies
  * How Your Information Is Used
  * Retaining and Destroying Your PD
  * Updating Your PD
  * Revoking Your Consent for Using Your PD
  * Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties
  * Do Not Track Settings
  * Links to Other Websites

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Generally, you control the amount and type of information that you provide to us when using our website. Our legal basis for collecting and processing your personal data (PD) on Signup Forms is based on consent.

**What Happens if you Don’t Give Us Your Personal Data (PD)?  **

If you do not provide us with enough PD, we may not be able to provide you with all our products and services. However, you can access and use most parts of our website without giving us your PD.

### WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA IN THE FOLLOWING WAYS

**_Automatic Information_**

We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our website, if any, as well as the name of the website you’ll visit when you leave our website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/the proxy server you use to access the Internet, your Internet service provider’s name, your web browser type, the type of mobile device, your computer operating system, and data about your browsing activity when using our website. We use all this information to analyze trends among our users to help improve our website.

**_When Entering and Using Our Website._** _ _

When you enter and use our website and agree to accept cookies, some of these cookies may contain your PD.

**_When subscribing as a user, Member registration or buying a service or product from our website_**

If you register as a subscriber, member, or buy a service we may collect some or all of the following information:  your first and last name, email address, physical address, credit card or other payment information and other information listed.

## Cookies

O4af.com uses cookies or similar technologies to store session information, analyze trends, administer the Sites, track users’ movements around the Sites, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. A A cookie is a small piece of data or a text file that is downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you access certain websites. Cookies may contain text that can be read by the web server that delivered the cookie to you. The text contained in the cookie generally consists of a sequence of letters and numbers that uniquely identifies your computer or mobile device; it may contain other information as well.  
You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. Please go to [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) for more information on cookies, including how to disable them. If you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our Sites or service.

**By agreeing to accept our use of cookies, you are giving us, and third parties we partner with, permission to place, store, and access some or all the cookies described below on your computer.**

**Strictly Necessary Cookies.**

These cookies are necessary for proper functioning of the website, such as displaying content, logging in, validating your session, responding to your request for services, and other functions. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of cookies. However, if you disable these cookies, you may not be able to access features on our website correctly or at all.

**Performance Cookies.  **

These cookies collect information about the use of the website, such as pages visited, traffic sources, users’ interests, content management, and other website measurements.

**Functional Cookies.  **

These cookies enable the website to remember user’s choices – such as their language, username, and other personal choices – while using the website. They can also be used to deliver services, such as letting a user make a blog post, listen to the audio, or watch videos on the website.

**Media cookies**

**Media cookies**  that can be used to improve a website’s performance and provide special features and content. They can be placed by third parties who provide services to us or by our company.

**Advertising or Targeting Cookies.  **

These cookies are usually placed and used by advertising companies to develop a profile of your browsing interests and serve advertisements on other websites that are related to your interests. You will see less targeted and more irrelevant advertising if you disable these cookies.

**We may also use cookies for:**

  * Identifying the areas of our website that you have visited
  * Personalizing content that you see on our website
  * Our website analytics
  * Remembering your preferences, settings, and login details
  * Targeted advertising and serving ads relevant to your interests
  * Affiliate marketing
  * Allowing you to post comments
  * Allowing you to share content with social networks

Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of cookies. However, if you disable cookies, you may not be able to access some features on our website correctly or at all.

In Addition to cookies, there are other similar technologies used by o4af.com

**Web Beacons**

We may also use a technology called web beacons to collect general information about your use of our website and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by web beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people who open our emails. Web beacons also help us to understand the behavior of our customers, members, and visitors.

**Social Widgets**

We may have buttons or icons provided by third-party social media providers that allow you to interact with those social media services when you view a webpage. These social widgets may collect browsing data, which may be received by the third party that provided the widget and are controlled by the third parties.

### Our Partners/ advertisers

Our website includes third-party advertising, and placement tracking technologies such as and not limited to cookies and etc. these advertising companies may use the technologies to collect the information about your visits to the websites. These statistics are used by these third party advertising companies to provide ads of relevance to you.

Our advertising partners such as **Google Adsense** and Ad Networks, may have the occasion to collect information in regards to your computer for our services. The information is gained in a statistical manner for our use or advertisers on our site. Data gathered will not identify you personally. It is strictly aggregate statistical data about our visitors and how they used our resources on the site. No identifying personal information will be shared at any time via cookies. You may elect to decline all cookies via your computer. Every computer has the ability to decline file downloads like cookies. Your browser has an option to enable the declining of cookies. Any of our advertisers may also have a use for cookies. We are not responsible, nor do we have control of the cookies downloaded from advertisements. They are downloaded only if you click on the advertisement.

Links on our site that belong to third parties may be found. These websites have their own Privacy Policy, which you agree to when you use the link to the site. You should read the third party’s policy. We do not accept claims of liability or responsibility in any way for these policies or links, as we have no way to control the third party sites.

### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party ad networks such as **Google Adsense** to either display advertising on our Site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites. This information is used to provide you targeted advertising across the internet, based upon your interests. If you are from European Economic Area (EEA), the ads networks will use cookies or mobile identifier to serve you non-personalized ads.

To Know more about how Google use the cookies, and how you can control the cookies please visit this link: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

**Google Analytics Privacy notice**. Our website uses Google Analytics to collect information about the use of our website. Google Analytics collects information from users such as age, gender, interests, demographics, how often they visit our website, what pages they visit, and what other websites they have used before coming to our website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to analyze traffic, remarket our products and services to users, improve our marketing, advertising, and to improve our website. We have enabled Google Analytics advertising features such as remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit our website, not your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected using Google Analytics with PD. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google also uses specific identifiers to help collect information about the use of our website. For more information on how Google collects and processes your data, visit <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

You can prevent Google Analytics from using your information by opting out at this link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

**Cookies** | **Provider** | **Description** | **Expiry** | **Type**  
---|---|---|---|---  
CookieConsent | o4af.com | Stores the user’s cookie consent state for the current domain | 1 year | HTTP  
__cfduid | onesignal.com | Used by the content network, Cloudflare, to identify trusted web traffic. | 1 year | HTTP  
_ga | O4af.com | Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website. | 2 years | HTTP  
_gat | O4AF.COM | Used by Google Analytics to throttle request rate | Session | HTTP  
_gid | o4af.com | Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website. | Session | HTTP  
|  |  |  |   
|  | **Cookies May be placed** |  |   
|  | Google ad-sense and other ad networks such as Double click.net will place the cookies for ads personalisation. |  |   
  
**HOW TO MANAGE COOKIES**

You have the ability to control the use of certain Cookie Technologies.

#### Opt-in and Opt-out on Browsers

When you use cPrime via a browser, you can change your web browser’s settings to reflect your cookie preferences for cookies directly from the site you are on or for third-party cookies. Each browser is a little different, but usually these settings are under the “options” or “preferences” menu. The links below provide information about cookie settings for the browsers supported by cPrime:

• Microsoft Edge  
• Internet Explorer  
• Firefox  
• Chrome  
• Safari

#### Opt-out of Third-Party Networks

If you do not wish to have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based advertisements, you may decline to receive interest based ads through Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), click here, (or if you are located in the European Union click here). Please note this does not stop you from being served advertisements. You will continue to receive generic advertisements. Please note that if you reject or block all cookies in your browser settings, you will not be able to take advantage of cPrime’s Service as some cookies are necessary for the Site to function properly.

#### Google Analytics Opt-out

For Google Analytics Advertising Features, you can opt-out through Google Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI’s consumer opt-out listed above). Google also provides a Google Analytics opt-out plug-in for the web.

#### Third-Party Tools

Various third parties provide browser plug-ins and apps that can help provide you information on, and limit or block, third-party cookies, web beacons, and some JavaScript-based technologies.

## Use of the information

We use the information we receive from you to:

  * Provide our products and services you have requested or purchased from us
  * Personalize and customize our content
  * Make improvements to our website
  * Contact you with updates to our website
  * Resolve problems and disputes
  * Contact you with marketing and advertising that we believe may be of interest to you

Your information will be used to contact you to inform you from latest changes and opportunities available on O4af.com

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect our rights or property.

We may share the non-personally identifiable information including the information submitted by you or automatically collected, publicly in the aggregated forms for any purpose including, but not limited to, research and marketing purposes, and our use and disclosure of such information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy.

O4af.com reserves the right to change privacy policy of the site, at any time and in its sole discretion. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes will constitute your acceptance of such changes. We encourage you to review the Site Privacy Policy whenever you visit this website.

While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of data, we will make efforts to meet them. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of data. In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

**Communications and Emails.  **

When we communicate with you about our website, we will use the email address you provided when you registered as a member or user. We may also send you emails with promotional information about our website or offers from us or our affiliates unless you have opted out of receiving such information. You can change your contact preferences at any time through your account or by sending us an email with your request to [opportunity4af@gmail.com](mailto:opportunity4af@gmail.com)

**Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties.  **

We do not sell or rent your PD to third parties for marketing purposes.

**Sharing Information with Facebook and Google for Marketing Purposes.  **

We may share your PD with third parties for similar audience marketing purposes. Similar audience marketing is also called lookalike audience marketing. The third parties we share your PD with for this type of marketing include Facebook and/or Google. Using your PD, for similar audience marketing or lookalike audience marketing helps us find new audiences (users and customers) based on similar interests to yours, this helps us improve our marketing services. Your PD is only shared with Facebook and Google for this type of marketing. By using our website and agreeing to our privacy notice, you are giving your consent for your PD to be used for the marketing purposes described in this section.

**Legally Required Releases of Information.  **We may be legally required to disclose your PD if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal processes; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties, including you and/or other users or members; or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of our company, users, employees, and affiliates.

## RETAINING AND DESTROYING YOUR PD

We retain information that we collect from you (including your PD) only for as long as we need it for legal, business, or tax purposes. Your information may be retained in electronic form, paper form, or a combination of both. When your information is no longer needed, we will destroy, delete, or erase it.

## UPDATING YOUR PD

You can update your PD using services found on our website. If no such services exist, you can contact us using the contact information found at the top of this notice and we will help you. However, we may keep your PD as needed to enforce our agreements and to comply with any legal obligations.

## REVOKING YOUR CONSENT FOR USING YOUR PD

You have the right to revoke your consent for us to use your PD at any time. Such an optout will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to affiliates and business partners, (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers that provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, computer system services, shipping, data management services, (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your requests, (iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments, or as otherwise required to be made under applicable law, (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties, or (vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent contests or promotions you may choose to enter, or third-party offers you may choose to accept. If you want to revoke your consent for us to use your PD, send us an email with your request to: Opportunity4af@gmail.com

## PROTECTING THE PRIVACY RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES

If any postings you make on our website contain information about third parties, you must make sure you have permission to include that information in your posting. While we are not legally liable for the actions of our users, we will remove any postings about which we are notified, if such postings violate the privacy rights of others.

## DO NOT TRACK SETTINGS

Some web browsers have settings that enable you to request that our website not track your movement within our website. Our website does not obey such settings when transmitted to and detected by our website. You can turn off tracking features and other security settings in your browser by referring to your browser’s user manual.

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to other websites. These websites are not under our control and are not subject to our privacy notice. These websites will likely have their own privacy notices. We have no responsibility for these websites and we provide links to these websites solely for your convenience. You acknowledge that your use of and access to these websites are solely at your risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy notices of these websites to see how they treat your PD.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at [opportunity4af@gmail.com](mailto:opportunity4af@gmail.com)
